{"showBridgeTasks":true,"__cache./api/resource/task/46400/?r_version=1":{"taskOid":46400,"taskName":"Universal Remote Control - Consolidate \u0026 Program","taskDescription":"Universal Remote Control Consolidation \u0026 Programming","xmTaskDescriptor":"Universal Remote Programming Pro","matchable":false,"profileable":true,"esScore":0.0,"defaultCostGuideTaskId":129,"active":true,"taskKeywords":"Universal controls programming remotes radio","textMessagingName":"Univ Remote","rolloverLongDesc":"Consolidates multiple remote controls in to one Universal Remote Control.  Includes programming new remote to perform macros or display custom device pages.","rolloverShortDesc":"Consolidation \u0026 Programming of Universal Remote Controls","sectorId":"HS","metaDescription":"Find local contractors to Consolidate and Program a Universal Remote Control.  HomeAdvisor will connect you with prescreened and customer-rated contractors in your area.","htmlTitle":"Program Universal Remote \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e","contentDescription":null,"pwcId":6,"acceptGoal":3,"multiZip":false,"preMatchTypeId":4,"bridgeTaskOid":0,"bridgeTaskText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkId":0,"bridgeTaskActive":"N","xmName":"Universal Remote Control Programming","redirectToTaskOid":-1,"spDisplayName":"Universal Remote Control - Consolidate \u0026 Program","xmHeaderDescriptor":"Describe Your Home Theater Project","urlName":"Universal-Remote-Control-Consolidate-Program","taskConsiderationId":1,"siteVisible":true,"attributeMatchable":true,"htmlTitleTloc":"\u003cspcount\u003e Best Universal Remote Progammers - \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | HomeAdvisor","searchKeywords":"Universal,controls,programming,remotes,radio,infrared,rf,ir,range,extended,control,zone,multi,lcd,automation,remote,screen,touch,consolidate,macro,remote","emcCategoryOid":-12006,"locationDisplayText":"What is the location of your project?","semLocationDisplayText":"To get started, enter the location of your project","commentsPromptText":"Please provide a short description of your project","primaryQuestionSetId":1309,"locationSpecific":false,"commercial":false,"viewFirstParentTask":false},"taskHeader":"Universal Remote Programming Pro","categoryPerformanceTest":true,"scrollyPathPageBase":"","providedPostalCode":"","hideAllSemIcons":false,"scrolly_persistedParams":{},"addressId":null,"AdobeFlickerMgmtOn":false,"SCROLLY_FILTER_NON_REQUIRED_33367":false,"headerBranding":{"src":"/images/consumer/cobranding/HA.svg","name":"ha"},"entryPointId":0,"matchingSourceId":2,"scrollyProgressBarTest":false,"isMobile":false,"consumer":{"entityId":0},"affiliateCode":"sm_def_sto","twoPageSubmit":true,"__cache./api/resource/task/interview/46400/":{"taskOID":46400,"originalTaskOID":46400,"setID":1309,"interviewType":"TASK_INTERVIEW","questions":[{"questionID":6415,"questionDisplayText":"Type of remote","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What kind of remote control would you like?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":8745,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Basic universal remote","answerDisplayText":"Basic universal remote","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8746,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Mid-range remote with some advanced features","answerDisplayText":"Mid-range remote with advanced features","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8747,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"High-end remote with ability to control any system","answerDisplayText":"High-end remote with ability to control any system","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":6416,"questionDisplayText":"Number of devices","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"How many devices do you want the remote to control?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":8748,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"1-3","answerDisplayText":"1-3","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8749,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"4-7","answerDisplayText":"4-7","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8750,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"8-10","answerDisplayText":"8-10","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8751,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 10","answerDisplayText":"More than 10","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":6417,"questionDisplayText":"Special Features","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What kind of special features would you like?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":8752,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Control multiple areas/zones","answerDisplayText":"Control multiple areas/zones","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8753,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Table-top remote","answerDisplayText":"Table-top remote","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8754,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Extended range","answerDisplayText":"Extended range","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8755,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Macro programming","answerDisplayText":"Macro programming","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8756,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Touch screen remote","answerDisplayText":"Touch screen remote","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8757,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Integration with Home Automation systems","answerDisplayText":"Integration with Home Automation systems","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":50001,"questionDisplayText":"Covered by Insurance","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Is this request covered by an insurance claim?","shortQuestionText":"Covered by an insurance claim?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":10020,"questionDisplayText":"Request is for Commercial Location","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":5,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Is this location a commercial location?","shortQuestionText":"Is this a commercial location?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}],"questionElements":[{"questionID":6415,"questionDisplayText":"Type of remote","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What kind of remote control would you like?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":8745,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Basic universal remote","answerDisplayText":"Basic universal remote","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8746,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Mid-range remote with some advanced features","answerDisplayText":"Mid-range remote with advanced features","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8747,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"High-end remote with ability to control any system","answerDisplayText":"High-end remote with ability to control any system","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":8745,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Basic universal remote","answerDisplayText":"Basic universal remote","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8746,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Mid-range remote with some advanced features","answerDisplayText":"Mid-range remote with advanced features","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8747,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"High-end remote with ability to control any system","answerDisplayText":"High-end remote with ability to control any system","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":6416,"questionDisplayText":"Number of devices","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"How many devices do you want the remote to control?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":8748,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"1-3","answerDisplayText":"1-3","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8749,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"4-7","answerDisplayText":"4-7","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8750,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"8-10","answerDisplayText":"8-10","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8751,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 10","answerDisplayText":"More than 10","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":8748,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"1-3","answerDisplayText":"1-3","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8749,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"4-7","answerDisplayText":"4-7","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8750,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"8-10","answerDisplayText":"8-10","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8751,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 10","answerDisplayText":"More than 10","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":6417,"questionDisplayText":"Special Features","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What kind of special features would you like?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":8752,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Control multiple areas/zones","answerDisplayText":"Control multiple areas/zones","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8753,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Table-top remote","answerDisplayText":"Table-top remote","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8754,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Extended range","answerDisplayText":"Extended range","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8755,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Macro programming","answerDisplayText":"Macro programming","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8756,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Touch screen remote","answerDisplayText":"Touch screen remote","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8757,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Integration with Home Automation systems","answerDisplayText":"Integration with Home Automation systems","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":8752,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Control multiple areas/zones","answerDisplayText":"Control multiple areas/zones","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8753,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Table-top remote","answerDisplayText":"Table-top remote","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8754,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Extended range","answerDisplayText":"Extended range","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8755,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Macro programming","answerDisplayText":"Macro programming","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8756,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Touch screen remote","answerDisplayText":"Touch screen remote","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8757,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Integration with Home Automation systems","answerDisplayText":"Integration with Home Automation systems","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":50001,"questionDisplayText":"Covered by Insurance","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Is this request covered by an insurance claim?","shortQuestionText":"Covered by an insurance claim?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":10020,"questionDisplayText":"Request is for Commercial Location","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":5,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Is this location a commercial location?","shortQuestionText":"Is this a commercial location?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}]},"sar":true,"scrolly_customDefaults":["50001_10002","8152_10002","30001_10002","160804_10002","20001_10002","160807_10002","160805_10002","502713_10002","160810_6938","8373_67562","8374_67566"],"entityId":0,"sessionId":"1564368210609pwspr010376737CC5AE756748174EA7F763C984D.pwspr010-1","shouldShowTasks":true,"KNOWN_USER_SCROLLY_TEST_SITE_33390":"ctrl","semThreeIcons":false,"isCookielessUser":true}